Guide to the Cornell University Cooperative Extension records, 1915-2009.
Cornell University Cooperative Extension records, 1915-2009.
- Series XI. Committees, Councils, Programs
  - 4-H
    - Memorandum of Agreement-New York College of Agriculture and the State Education Department concerning Junior Extension (4-H Club) Work, 1926 (Box 84, Folder 7)
    - Federal Extension Service Address-4-H Club Leaders' Conference-C.B. Smith, Director, 1932 (Box 84, Folder 8)
    - 4-H Club and Older Youth Studies-Extension Service,U.S.D.A, 1940-1941 (Box 84, Folder 9)
    - Urban 4-H Work-Coats and Clark, 1947, 1956 (Box 84, Folder 10)
    - National 4-H Club Center-Report of the Core Committee, 1948-1950 (Box 84, Folder 10A)
    - County Farm and Home Bureau and 4-H Club Association-"Appropriations for Two Contiguous Counties", 1952 (Box 84, Folder 11)
    - National 4-H Foundation, 1952-1961 (Box 84, Folder 12)
    - National 4-H Foundation-Various reports, including Annual and Progress Reports, 1950-1969 (Box 84)
    - Significance of the 4-H Conservation Training Camp and the Future Development of the Training Center- A.H. Peterson, 1957 (Box 84, Folder 13)
    - Cornell University-4-H Extension Club Constitution, 1957 (Box 84, Folder 14)
    - "Career Exploration"-4-H Club Program, 1959-1961 (Box 84, Folder 15)
    - 4-H Club Work in Urban Areas, 1960 (Box 84, Folder 16)
    - Report of the 4-H Task Force-Situation and Recommendations, 1968 (Box 75, Folder 33)
    - Activewear Advantage Grant - Charlotte Coffman, Huiju Park and Eric Beaudette, 2014 (Box 89, Folder 12)
  - Various other Committees and Programs
    - New York State Community Theatre Association, 1914-1958 (Box 84, Folder 17)
    - Educational Policy and Methods in Extension Service Committee- College Preparation for Extension Service in Agriculture and Homemaking in New York State, 1925 (Box 85, Folder 1A)
    - Report of the Measuring Stick Committee, 1933 (Box 80, Folder 17)
    - Land Use Planning Committee-Minutes of Meetings, 1939 (Box 84, Folder 18)
    - Land Use Planning Committee-Minutes of Meetings, 1939-1941 (Box 84, Folder 19)
    - Land Use Planning Committee-A Unified State Agricultural Program to Meet the Impacts of War, 1941 (Box 84, Folder 20)
    - Extension Wartime Council-Minutes of Meetings, 1942-1945 (Box 84, Folder 21)
    - Committee on Construction and Remodeling of Farm Homes, 1944-1951 (Box 80, Folder 23)
    - Sub-Committee on Extension Training of the Resident Educational Policies Committee in the New York State College of Home Economics-Report, 1945 (Box 84, Folder 27)
    - New York State Policy Committee-History, 1946 (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - New York State Policy Committee-Reports, 1944-1946 (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - New York State Policy Committee-Membership (includes photo), 1944-1946 (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - New York State Policy Committee- meeting minutes and suggestions for action to counties, 1946-03 (Box 80, Folder 9)
    - New York State Policy Committee-Shapley's Report to Simons, 1946 (Box 80, Folder 10)
    - New York State Agricultural Mobilization Committee-Consolidation of Offices, 1946-1959 (Box 84, Folder 22)
    - Extension Public Affairs Committee, 1947-1961 (Box 84, Folder 28)
    - Committee on Migratory Farm Labor, 1948 (Box 84, Folder 29)
    - Land-Grant College Committee on Training for Government Service, 1948-1959 (Box 84, Folder 30)
    - Young Adult and Rural Youth Program, 1949-1961 (Box 84, Folder 31)
    - Personnel Policies Committee, State University of New York (Catherwood Report), 1950 (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - District Engineers Committee on Policy, 1952 (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - Puerto Rico-Food Advisory Commission, 1952-1954 (Box 80, Folder 24-25)
    - Adult Education Committee-Report, 1953 (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - General Education Committee-Report to the Faculty of the College of Agriculture, 1953 (Box 85, Folder 4)
    - Spray Residues-Programs, 1953-1960 (Box 85, Folder 5)
    - Indian Affairs/American Indian (Box 85, Folder 6-8)
      Indian Affairs Program, 1954-1955
      E.A. Bates-Work with Indians, 1945-1962
      U.S. Dept. of Agriculture-Indians, 1958
    - American Indian Program, 1988-2000 (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - Farm and Home Management-Memos, Reports, Papers, 1954-1957 (Box 80, Folder 21-22)
    - Farm and Home Management Steering Committee, 1955-1961 (Box 85, Folder 9)
    - Farm and Home Management Steering Committee-Minutes of Meetings, 1956-1959 (Box 85, Folder 10)
    - Long Range Development Program-New York State, 1957-1958 (Box 85, Folder 11)
    - Gypsy Moth Control Program, 1957-1960 (Box 85, Folder 12)
    - Joint Legislative Committee on Metropolitan Areas-Rural Government, 1958 (Box 85, Folder 13)
    - College Poultry Committee-Extension Program, 1958 (Box 85, Folder 14)
    - Rural Sociology Workshop Committee, 1958-1960 (Box 85, Folder 15)
    - Forage Program Committee, 1959 (Box 85, Folder 16)
    - New York State Extension Service Advisory Council, 1959-07 (Box 85, Folder 17)
    - Committee of 16, 1950-1969 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      Reorganization that resulted in Country Extension Service Associations due to separation from Farm Bureau.
    - Farm and Home Management Program, 1950-1969 (Box 4, Folder 2-3)
      Federally funded in 1954; with budgets, annual reports, etc.
    - Drought Program, 1962-1966 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Dairy Cattle Purchases by Mexico (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Rural Development Program - Low Income Families. Camden, Oneida County., 1950-1969 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - North Country Research and Extension, 1964-1966 (Box 4, Folder 7)
      Drainage Research and Demonstration Program. Cornell Tour, 1964
    - Project M. (Comprehensive program to improve milk quality at the farm), 1950-1969 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Committee on Extension Studies (List of completed studies, etc.), 1950-1969 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Television Film Center Advisory Committee, 1950-1969 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Oral History Advisory Committee, 1950-1969 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Community Resource Development, 1950-1969 (Box 4)
    - Area Redevelopment Administration. (Federal Aid to Communities.), 1950-1969 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Broome County Rural Development Program, 1950-1969 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Natural Resource Development, 1950-1969 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Operation Advance, 1950-1969 (Box 4, Folder 15-16)
    - Rural Areas Development, 1950-1969 (Box 4, Folder 17-18)
    - Farm Policy Council, 1960 (Box 85, Folder 18)
    - International Agricultural Development Program at the College of Agriculture-John Mellor, 1961 (Box 85, Folder 19)
    - Operation Advance, 1961 (Box 85, Folder 20)
    - Agricultural Science Youth Program, 1961-03 (Box 85, Folder 21)
    - Extension Committee on Organization and Policy-Abstract of Policy Statements, 1962 (Box 85, Folder 21)
    - New York State Agents Meeting-Notes from Various Committees, 1967 (Box 86, Folder 20)
    - Programs in Population, Family Planning, and Sex Education, 1972-1975 (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - Cornell Cooperative Extension Forum (CCEF), 198(?)-1993 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Cornell Cooperative Extension Forum (CCEF), 1982-1997 (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - Scholarship Committee, 1988-2002 (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - Cornell Cooperative Extension Recruitment Advisory Committee, 1989 (Box 74, Folder 7A)
    - Land Grant and Statutory Colleges Affairs Committee, 1989-1999 (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - Internationalizing Cornell Cooperative Extension Focus Group, 1995-1999 (Box 74, Folder 9)
    - Land Grant Mission Extension Panel, 2001-2002 (Box 74, Folder 10)
    - Awareness Program (Box 74, Folder 11)
    - Programs - Summary Sheets, 2008 (Box 89, Folder 11)
    - Cornell Cooperative Extension Centennial, 2011 (Box 89, Folder 26)